Guide to the Central Asia Fellowship Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum - 2015, Series XI
  - Publications and program material
    - Audio-visual material
      - A2301sh, A2401, A4401Ts (Box 30, Folder 6)
        A2301sh: Sherpa Gospel Songs; A2401: Amdo worship 1 & 2, CD; A4401Ts:God's Story - From Creation to Eternity (Tshangla)
      - V1001, V1002, V1002N, V1005, V1006, Unclassified (Box 30, Folder 7)
        V1001: Tsering of the Khamba, DVD; V1002: Hope; V1002N: Hope (NTSC); V1005: Jerem's Adventure; V1006: Annala's Story
      - V3001: Good news for you (red coloured, big); V3002: Good news for you (red coloured, small) (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Unclassified (3) (Box 31, Folder 2)
        Unclassified: Story of Jesus: According to Luke (DVD) Unclassified: DVD MP3; Unclassified Qiangic Speaking Tibetans (CD)
      - Posters (Box OV1)
        V2003: Prodigal Son (Poster); V2003S: Prodigal Son - Small A3 Size; V2003V: Prodigal Son (Poster, Small in vinyl); V2005: Power of Jesus (Poster); V2007: Christmas Story (Poster); V2008: Church Order and Explanation (Poster); V2009: Tibetan Art, Can a mother forget..., color (Poster); V2013s: Christian Thanka (small); V2014: Khamba people (Poster); V2015:Small boy (Poster); V2016: Who is Your Neighbor?; Posters, Health Laminated, A4 paper size (4 kinds)
- Addendum - 2017, Series XII
  - Audio/Media/Visual
    - Christmas Kham Tibetan Gospel Songs (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Rise and Shine (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Songs and stories for children to introduce the gospel in Lhomi /Publisher: First Love South Asia
    - Rising River Music & Testimonies by Aradhna (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Rewa Hope (4 languages) (Box 38, Folder 2)
      DVD in Tibetan based on the Hope story from Mars Hill Productions. Tibetan music, songs and dance.
    - Rewa Hope DVD Amdo (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Rewa Hope DVD Dege (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Rewa Hope DVD Mandarin (Box 38, Folder 2)
      DVD in Manadrin (also contains Tibetan) based on the Hope story from Mars Hill Productions. Tibetan music, songs and dance.
  - Books and Booklets
    - Give me this mountain! (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tibetan Tales by Suzanne, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tibetan Tales vol.2, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Voices from the Past, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      A brief overview of the history of Christian & Missionary Alliance workers in Qinghai who were called to reach Tibetan people with the gospel.
    - ZHABSTOG - Serving and celebrating god's faithfulness over the years (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Church history in short over the Moravian church to Tibetan peoples
    - Experience of Being Forced into Marriage in Lhomi, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Journey to the Terai in Lhomi, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Restored to Freedom from Fear, Guilt, and Shame: Lessons from the Buddhist World (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Christian Missionaries and Tibet (Lungta), 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      A magazine article giving an overview of the history of missions in Tibet from a Tibetan exile (non-Christian) view point, this paper includes short biographies of different missionaries and their impact on Tibetan culture.
    - God Spoke Tibetan, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Sharing Christ in the Tibetan Buddhist World, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - The Story of Drolma: Daughter of Tibet, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Ministry to Tibetan Buddhists (Magazine) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - How the Lord Led my Life inside Tibet, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Commentary on the Lord's Prayer in Tibetan, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Commentary on the Lord's Prayer in Tibetan & Chinese, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Commentary on the Lord's Prayer in Tibetan & English, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Jesus the Christ/Tibetan, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Study guide. Discipleship.
    - Questions and Answers about Christianity in Tibetan & Chinese, 2016 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Questions and Answers about Christianity in Tibetan & English, 2016 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Way of Truth, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      General Discipleship training book for new believers.
    - The Way of Truth, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The Way of Truth, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Introduction to the Almighty JHVE (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Life without Father, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Healing the Wounds of Trauma; How the Church Can Help, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Children Focus
    - Beginners Bible in multilingual (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - A Selection of Great Bible Stories Trilingual Version, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Children coloring book (stories from the bible) in Dzongkha (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Jesus Savior Amdo Children CD, 2014 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Story of Children in Lhomi, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Gifts / Publicity
    - Journey on Foot Calendar: Birthday & Anniversaries reminder, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Tibetan Calendar 2014, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Tibetan Calendar 2015, 2014 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Tibetan Calendar 2016, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Tibetan Bible Website card Chinese (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Tibetan Bible Website card English (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Home treatment- Rabies Prevention etc (Tibetans), 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Kunde Foundation
    - Sanitation Without Water, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Nelhos - For Social Transformation (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Language
    - A collection of Lhomi Poems, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Nepal Lhomi Society -Nelhos
    - A collection of Lhomi proverbs, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Being Older Does Not Prevent Education in Lhomi, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Mother Tongue Centre Nepal
    - English For Beginner (Extra exercise), 2012 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Guarding Crops from Monkeys in Lhomi, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Lhomi - Nepali Advance Literacy, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Lhomi Folk Stories - Part One, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Lhomi Primer Book 1, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Lhomi Primer Book 2, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Saral Nepali For Advance literacy course, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Social - Science and Health (For Advance literacy course), 2011 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Stories and Songs of Lhomi village (Lhomi literacy reading materials, Stage 1), 2010 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Stories from the Bible - An English Textbook for Tibetans (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Gsungrab.org
    - Stories from the Bible; An English Textbook for Tibetans Part 2, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Tibetan script for Lhomi, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Music
    - Lhomi Gospel Songbook, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Ghangri Church, Kathmandu
    - From the darkness to the light in Dzongkha (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Lowa Fellowship
    - From the darkness to the light in Dzongkha (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Praise & Worship Songs in Dzongkha, Tshangla, Khengkha, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      EHLLP
    - Tibetan Songbook (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - A collection of Traditional Lhomi Songs and Dances, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Stories and Songs of our village (Lhomi literacy reading materials, Stage 3), 2010 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Prayer Materials
    - New Beginnings: Three days of prayer for buddha (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Scripture
    - Khengkha NT (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Lhomi New Testament (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - New Tibetan Bible (NTB): Tibetan NT, 2015 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Sherpa NT, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Tshangla NT, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Exploring the way to Eternal life with Tibetan (CT), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Exploring the Way to Eternal Life with Tibetans (CT-Chinese) 2013 2nd edition new version (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Genesis stories with CD (CT/Chinese) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - God's Word for Lowa (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Gospel of John (Tibetan language) 2nd edition, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Gospel of Luke & Acts (CT-LL), 2012, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Gospel of Mark (CT-LL) 2nd edition, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Gospel of Mark Trial Version: Amdo language, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Gospel of Matthew, Old Classical (Tibetan language), 1984 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Gospel written by Apostle John And 1st, 2nd & 3rd Letter written by Apostle John (in Colloquial Ladakhi), 2014 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - A Bible Handbook - Tibetan, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Exploring the Bible with Tibetans, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Exploring the Good News of Grace With Tibetans (CT-Chinese) 2013 2nd edition new version (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Jesus Christ has Power to Save Us, 2016 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Oral Bible Stories Sherpa (Pre-version), 2014 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Tracts
    - 10 commandment (Box 38)
    - A Buddhist Monk's Life Story (Box 38)
    - Build your house on the Rock, Jesus (Box 38)
    - Creation tract in Dzongkha (Box 38)
    - Daily Strength: Savior of the World, 31-day guide (Box 38)
    - Encountering the Eternal Guru/ 10 True Stories (Box 38)
    - From the darkness to the light in Dzongkha (Box 38)
    - God's word: Gospel for Himalayas (Box 38)
    - He is a Creator or a Liar in Dzongkha (Box 38)
    - I Have Done It for All (Box 38)
    - Isa 9:2 Card (Box 38)
    - Isa 9:2 Bookmark (Box 38)
    - Jesus Christ is the only one between God and Human being in Dzongkha (Box 38)
    - Peace in Tsangla (Box 38)
    - Story of Creation in Ladakhi (Modern version) (Box 38)
    - The Unknown God/One Men's Story (Box 38)
    - The Way to Heaven, Chinese (Box 38)
    - The Way to Heaven, Russian (Box 38)
    - NELHOS - Nepal Lhomi Society Information Pamphlet (Box 38)
  - Restricted files
    The listings for this subseries are restricted. Contact the repository for more information.